[Music]
the world is
changing and investors around the world
are becoming more sophisticated
demanding innovative solutions from
wealth and asset managers
combining our deep expertise and
experience in both investment and wealth
management
manulife investment management offers
fully integrated solutions
spanning investment funds and pensions
globally
strategically positioned in key markets
our investment and client service
operations
are supported by seasoned investment
professionals across the globe
today we are one of the leading global
wealth and asset managers
what sets us apart is our three
complementary global business lines
to meet the unique needs of our clients
with our multi-product and multi-channel
offerings our retail investments arm
brings
institutional capabilities to retail
investors
creating unparalleled investment
solutions
while our institutional asset management
arm provides a comprehensive suite of
outcome-oriented solutions to
institutions
internationally our retirement arm
offers an
open architecture platform which aims at
providing best-in-class products
and end-to-end solutions to meet the
varied retirement needs
leveraging the strength of our parent
company manulife financial corporation
which has a rich heritage and investment
track record that dates back to the
1800s
we have access to a wealth of experience
with our strong insurance pedigree we
manage risks in a strategic and dynamic
way
[Music]
in asia our unrivaled presence and deep
understanding of the region
enable us to offer strong local insights
and flexibility in customizing solutions
for every client
it is our unwavering commitment in asia
that makes us a trusted partner of many
across the world
leveraging our local level expertise as
well as extensive global resources and
network
we deliver solid investment results not
just in public markets
but also private markets
our long track record and deep
capabilities in private assets
means you can tap into a diverse group
of assets
to meet your unique investment needs
through our differentiated value-added
public and private asset offerings and
capabilities
we punch above our weight in delivering
outcome-oriented
and goal-based investment solutions to
our clients
we achieve excellence in hong kong
where we power the largest mandatory
provident fund provider
manulife and china where we are the
first financial institution to receive
the investment company
wholly for an owned entity license
the philippines where we are the first
trust corporation
backed by a leading multinational
financial services group
and indonesia where we were awarded the
top
fund house
and this sums up our commitment to you
manulife investment management